# Jo'Vontae Coleman

Beloit, WI 53511 colemanjovontae@gmail.com +1 608 718 2352

I am 22 years old. I possess the worth of my youth in drive, a dependable mindset and a work ethic only matched by my willingness to learn.

I aspire to join an established (or developing) work culture where we will: produce quality product and/ or services, preform tasks safely and efficiently, and grow consistently.

Although it remains undecided thus far, I do aspire to specialize in an area one day. I frequently study web development and computer programming. I know my potential is that of a seasoned computer scientist if all my attributes are fully applied. I also possess the physical capabilities and mental fortitude fit for laborious tasks.

Considering the aforementioned, I do not have many boundaries surrounding WHERE I start. How and when I start are more relevant preoccupations to me.

My biggest concerns in deciding my ideal professional environment include safety and growth. I may not be the most experienced in a world where my competitors are 20+ years my senior, but to those willing to teach, I am even more willing to learn. As long as the work culture perpetuates safe, strong habits, growth can happen steadily and comfortably!

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

## Work Experience

#### **Comcast Technician**

SPX Flow-Delavan, WI March 2024 to Present

During my tenure at Comcast in the foundry department at SPX Flow, my primary roles included operating and maintaining the foundry equipment, monitoring the casting process for quality and efficiency, and ensuring that all safety protocols were strictly adhered to. Additionally, I was responsible for inspecting and finishing cast metal products, as well as participating in quality control processes to ensure the production of high-quality components. I also actively contributed to the maintenance of equipment and tools to uphold optimal performance and efficiency in the foundry environment. These responsibilities allowed me to develop a strong understanding of the intricacies of metal casting and the importance of quality control in a manufacturing setting.

#### **Concrete Laborer**

Mid-States Concrete Industries-South Beloit, IL May 2023 to March 2024

During my experience at Mid-States Concrete, I was engaged in a variety of concrete-related tasks. This included sandblasting and working in the berms area, where I managed trailers of freshly poured precast pieces. My responsibilities extended to performing concrete patches, using power tools like grinders to cut rebar, torches for burning and patching flush cuts with a concrete mix, and utilizing scrapers and trowels to assist with concrete mixing and application. Additionally, I undertook tasks such as patching, rubbing, and Ardexing pieces to ensure quality workmanship.

## **Forklift Operator**

Morgan Truck Body-Janesville, WI November 2022 to April 2023

I operated fork machine equipment and was trained on inventory systems. I managed to preform all tasks efficiently through varying outside conditions.

#### Education

## **Sophomore in Psychology**

University of Wisconsin-Milwaukee - Milwaukee, WI August 2019 to August 2021

## High school diploma or GED

Beloit Turner High School - Beloit, WI November 2015 to June 2019

### Skills

- Door-to-Door Experience
- Cooking
- Leadership
- Food Preparation
- · Customer Service
- Assembly
- Forklift
- Concrete finishing (2 years)
- Communication skills
- Precision measuring instruments
- Calipers
- Micrometer
- Crane
- Soldering

## Certifications and Licenses

#### **Driver's License**

#### **Forklift Certification**